Wolf, Benjamin Papers 5477
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Benjamin Wolf Papers
1965-1979
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Wolf, Benjamin
5477
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
Arbitration, mediation and fact-finding reports. Includes many cases concerning the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the Brooklyn Union Gas Company, and the Transport Workers of America.
5652963
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 08, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 13, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Arbitrator, labor mediator and attorney; visiting professor, New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Cornell University. Wolf served as permanent arbitrator between the New York City Board of Education and the United Federation of Teachers; New York City and the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME); the New York City Off-Track Betting Corp. and AFSCME; New York State and AFSCME; the State University of New York and the Senate Professional Association; A. Goodman and the American Bakery and Confectionery Workers' Union; and between the Simmons Company and the Upholsterers International Union. Wolf also served as impartial chairman for American Airlines and the Transport Workers Union of America; the men's shirt industry and the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; and the Brooklyn Union Gas Company and the Transport Workers Union of America.
Born May 6, 1909. Attended Cornell University (B.A. 1930; LL.B. 1932).
Formerly labor mediator, New York State Board of Meidation; labor relations examiner, N.Y.S. Labor Relations Board.
Affiliated with National Academy of Arbitrators (board of governors 1971-; regional chairman 1967-1968); Industrial Relations Research Association; Society for Professionals in Dispute Resolution; New York Bar Association. On rosters of American Arbitration Association, Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, National Mediation Board, New York State Board of Mediation, New Jersey State Board of Mediation, New York Public Employment Relations Board, New Jersey Public Employment Relations Commission.
Arbitrator under contract for N.Y. City Board of Education and UFT; City of New York and District Council 37; OTB and DC37; N.Y. State and Council 82, AFSCME: State University of New York and Senate Professional Association; Metropolitan New York Milk Industry and IBT; New Rochelle Board of Education and UFT; A. Goodman & Sons and BCWU; Metropolitan Association of Optical Wholesalers and IUE; Simons Co. and Local 420, UIU.
Impartial Chairman; American Airlines and TWU, Men's Shirt Industry and ACWA; Brooklyn Union Gas and TWU; Williams Press and Pressmen's Union; Hiring Hall & Club Employees Union (Local 16); Westchester County Laundry Board of Trade and Local 335 IBT: Rochdale Village, Inc. and Local 90 Public Service Union; Ossining Board of Education and Ossining Teachers Association; Schwartz Laboratories, Inc. and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers; Ross Oil Term. Corp., Howard Fuel Corp. & Local 365 UAW.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5305: Benjamin H. Wolf Papers 5511: Benjamin Wolf Additional Papers 5539: Benjamin H. Wolf Additional Arbitration Files 5803: Benjamin Wolf Additional Arbitration Files
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States.; Mediation and conciliation, Industrial -- United States.; Collective labor agreements -- United States.; Wolf, Benjamin H., b. 1909
5652963
- City of New York vs. Local 3, IBEW (Fire Alarm Dispatchers), 6/12/72, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  #72-56 Settlement of Negotiations, Fact-Finder's Notes, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation
- Algro Knitting Mills vs. Local 1363, TWUA, 8/9/72, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  #72-57 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Improper Personal Conduct
- Buddah Records-Skye Recording Co., Ltd. Vs. AFTRA, 7/19/72 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  #72-58 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Memo from Both Parties on Stipulation as to Facts, Employee Practice, Correspondence - financial Irresponsibility
- Washex Machinery Corp. vs. District 15, IAM, 7/25/72, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  #72-59 Decision, Arbitrator's notes, Employee Exhibit, joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Sick Pay, Contract Interpretation
- Ward Leonard Electric Co. vs. District 3, IUE, 10/72, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  #72-60 Correspondence - Arbitration Withdrawn
- Westinghouse Electric Corp. vs. Local 410, IUE, 1/73, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  [Folder entitled 6(A-B)] #72-61 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcript, Employer Post-Hearing Brief, Employee Post-Hearing Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Post Arbitration Award, Correspondence - Improper Job Attitud
- Breyer Ice Cream vs. Local 757, IBT, 7/5, 12/22/72, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  [Folder entitled 7(A-B)] #72-62 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Tardiness, Falsification, Medical Examinations
- Friendly Frost, Inc. vs. Local 814, IBT, 8/10/72, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  #72-63 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Leaves of Absences, Reinstatement
- Springfield Board of Education vs. Springfield Education Association, 8/21/72, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  #72-64 Report of Fact & Recommendation, Fact- Finder's Notes, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation
- City of New York vs. Local 144, SEIU, 11/24/72, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  E#72-65 Report of Fact & Recommendations, Fact-Finders Notes, Hearing Transcript, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation
- Holy Cross High School vs. Local 1776, Association of Catholic Teachers, AFT, 4/12/74, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  #72-66 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Submission, Employee Brief, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Arbitrability, Timeliness, Discrimination, Salary Increments
- Mamaroneck Board of Education vs. Mamaroneck Teachers Association, 10/12/72, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  [Folder entitled 2(A-B)] #72-67 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee's Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Revised School Budget, Correspondence - Leaves of Absence, Contract Interpretation
- Jelrus Technical Products vs. Local 102, IUE, 12/7/72, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  #72-68 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Seniority, Promotion, Work Stoppage & Slowdown, Past Practice
- Sunshine Fruit Juice Co. vs. Local 102, IBT, 2/73, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  #72-69 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Civil Action Summons, Petition for Removal, Past Arbitration Awards, Correspondence - Arbitrability, Grievance Procedure, Shutdown
- J.G. Tilp, Inc. vs. Moldmakers & Associated Workers Independent Union, 8/72, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  #72-70 Correspondence
- Dow Jones Wall Street Journal vs. Local 11, Newark Mailers Union, 7/28/72, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  #72-71 Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties During Hearing
- Riegel Paper Co. vs. Local 712, UPP, 9/8/72, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  [Folder entitled 6(A-D)] #72-72 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Brief, Employer Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Arbitrability, Improper Personal Conduct
- Bendix Corp. vs. Local 4831, USA, 11/9/72 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  [Folder entitled 7(A-D)] #72-73 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Pre-Hearing Brief, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Cost of Living Increases, Vacation Pay
- L. Batlin & Son, Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 8/31/72, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  [Folder entitled 1(A-B)] #72-74 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Dishonesty
- Valco Reproduction & Mailing Service, Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 8/31/72, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  [Folder entitled 2(A-B)] #72-75 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Sick Days
- J.G. Tilp, Inc. vs. Moldmakers & Associated Workers Industrial Union, 9/15/72, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  #72-76 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Absences
- ITT Continental Baking Co. vs. Local 50, BCW, 10/3/72, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  #72-77 Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- Ardsley Central School Dist. No. 5 vs. Ardsley federation of Teachers, 9/22/72, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  #72-78 Report of Fact & Recommendations, Fact-Finder's Notes, Correspondence - Absences
- ITT World Communications, Inc. vs. CWA, 3/15/73, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  #72-79 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcripts, Employer Post-Hearing Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits Arbitration Award, Correspondence - Classification of Jobs, Past Practice
- Winthrop Laboratories, Div. of Sterling Drugs, Inc. vs. Local 61, ICWU, 1/24/73, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  [Folder entitled 7(A-D)] #72-80 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Post-Hearing Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Lay off, Bumping, Seniority
- Ashland Chemical Co. vs. Local 22026, FLU, 10/2/72, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  #72-89 Hearing Transcript - Altercation
- Sterling Winthrop Research Institute, Div. of Sterling Drug, Inc. vs. Local 61, ICWU, 5/23/73, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  [Folder entitled 9(A-C)] #unknown, Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Submission, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Assignment of Job
- Manhattan Shirt Co. vs. ACWA, 11/2/67, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  [Folder entitled 1(A-B)] #S-3 Decision Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Miscellaneous Exhibits, Correspondence - Wages
- Gant Shirtmakers vs. Local 125, ACWA, 7/3/67, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  #S-11 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Improper Personal Conduct
- Cluett, Peabody & Co., Inc. vs. ACWA, 7/3/67, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  #S-11 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibit, Correspondence - Transfer Policy
- Manhattan Shirt Co. vs. AACWA, 5/16/68, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  [Folder entitled 4(A-D)] #S-13 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employers Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Reply Brief, Employee Reply Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Piecework, Wage Rates
- McGregor-Doniger, Inc. vs. ACWA, 10/9/67, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  #S-20 Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- Adamsville Shirt Manufacturing Co. vs. ACWA (Box 47, Folder 6)
  #S-22 (See 47-9, #S-25)
- Adamsville Shirt Manufacturing Co. vs. ACWA (Box 47, Folder 7)
  #S-23 (See 47-9, #S-25)
- Adamsville Shirt Manufacturing Co. vs. ACWA (Box 47, Folder 8)
  #S-24 (See 47-9, #S-25)
- Adamsville Shirt Manufacturing Co. vs. ACWA, 8/13/68, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  #S-25 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibit, joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Issues S-22 Absences; S-23 Settled During Hearing; S-24 Rates of Pay; S-25
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA, 11/2/67, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  #S-27 Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- Manhattan Shirt Co. vs. ACWA, 11/13/67, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  #S-32 Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- Kayler Manufacturing Co. vs. Local 962 ACWA, 6/10/68, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  Decision Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Piecework, Rates of Pay, Past Practice, Timework
- Roane County Manufacturing Co. vs. Local 962, 6/10/68, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  #S-37 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - Insubordination
- Cluett, Peabody & Co.., vs. ACWA (Box 47, Folder 14)
  #S-38 (See 47-19, S-45) - Reporting Pay
- Cluett, Peabody & Co., ACWA (Box 47, Folder 15)
  #S-41 (See 47-19, #S-45) - Overtime Pay
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA (Box 47, Folder 16)
  #S-42, (See 47-19, #S-45) - Rates of Pay
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA (Box 47, Folder 17)
  #S-43, (See 47-19, #S-45) - Disputes in Collar Department
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA (Box 47, Folder 18)
  #S-44 (See #S-57 for Decision) (See 47-19, #S-45) - Layoff
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA 11/9/68 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  #S-45, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Correspondence - #S-38 Reporting Pay; #S-41 Overtime; #S-42 Rates of Pay; #S-43 Dispute in Collar Dept.; #S-44 Layoff; #S-45 Layoff (Seniority)
- Apparel Corp. of America vs. ACWA (Box 48, Folder 1)
  #S-53 (See 48-2, #S-54) Improper Job Attitude, Incompetence
- Apparel Corp. of America vs. ACWA, 11/18/68, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  #S-54 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - Fights & Altercations
- Apparel Corp. of America vs. ACWA (Knoxville) 9/20/69, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  #S-55 Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - Rates of Pay
- Apparel Corp. of America vs. ACWA (Knoxville) 10/68, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  #S-56 Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - Incompetence & Inefficiency
- Cluett, Peabody & Co., Inc. Vs. ACWA, 11/9/68 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  #S-57 (See 47-19, #S-45 for Exhibits) Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - S-44 Layoff, Seniority; S-45 Layoff, Seniority; S-57 Seniority
- Publix Shirt Co. vs. ACWA, 2/8/69, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  #S-58 Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Incompetence
- Alabama Textile Corp. vs. ACWA (Andalusia) 1/69, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  #S-61 Correspondence - Layoffs
- Manhattan Shirt Co. vs. ACWA, 5/2/69, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  #S-65 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Correspondence - Plant Rules, Automation, Compensation
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA (Albertsville, Ala.) 6/3/70, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  #S-67 (See 48-22, #S-81) Promotion
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA (Albertsville, Ala.) 9/9/69, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  #S-68 (See 48-22, #S-81) Seniority, Reduction in Pay
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA (Albertville, Ala.), 1969 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  #S-69 (See 48-22, #S-81) Rates of Pay
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA (Albertville, Ala.) 9/9/69, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  #S-70 (See 48-22, #S-81) Seniority, Reduction in Pay
- Manhattan Shirt Co. (Winnsboro, SC) vs. ACWA, 8/18/69, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employer Exhibit, Correspondence - Wage Rates, Incentive System
- Manhattan Shirt Co. vs. ACWA (Charleston, SC) 6/30/69, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  #S-72 (See 48-16, #S-74) Incentive Systems
- Manhattan Shirt Co. vs. ACWA (Charleston, SC) 6/30/69, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  #S-73 (See 48-16, #S-74) Time Studies
- Manhattan Shirt Co. vs. ACWA (Charleston, SC) 6/30/69, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  [Folder entitled 16(A-B)] #S-74 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - #S-72 Incentive Systems; #S-73 Time Studies; S-74 Rates of Pay, Time Studies
- Manhattan Shirt Co. vs. ACWA (Americus, Ga.) 6/69, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  #S-75 Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - Time Study, Wage Rates
- M. Nirenberg & Sons, (Adamsville, Tenn.) vs. ACWA, 6/13/69, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Bargaining Unit, Improper Job Attitude
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. (Troy, NY), 6/29/69, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  #S-77 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - Transfers, Negligence
- Manhattan Shirt Co. vs. ACWA (Lexington, NC), 6/3/69, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  #S-78 Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA (Albertville, Ala.) 9/9/69, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  #S-80 (See 48-22, #S-81) Holiday Pay
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA (Albertville, Ala.) 9/9/69, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  [Folder entitled 22(A-C)] #S-81 Decisions, Arbitrator's Notes, employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - #S-67 Promotion; #S-68 Seniority, Reduction in Pay; #S-69 Rates of Pay; #S-70 Seniority, Reduction in Pay; #S-80 Holiday Pay; #S-81 Holiday
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. (Troy, NY) vs. ACWA, 9/25/69, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  #S-85 (See 48-24, #S-86) Piecework, Incentive Systems
- C.F. Hathaway Co. vs. ACWA (Waterville, Maine), 9/3/70, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  #S-103 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Interpretation, Bargaining History, Piecework
- F. Jacobson & Sons, Inc. vs. ACWA, 6/2/70, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  #S-104 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Vacations, Layoff
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA, 8/28/70, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  #S-105 (See 49-18, #S-111) Lay off
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA, 8/28/70, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  #S-106 (See 49-18. #S-111) Rates of Pay
- McGregor Donniger Co. vs. ACWA (Dover, NJ), 7/16/70, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  #S-107 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Holiday Questionnaire, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Holiday Pay
- Manhattan Shirt Co. vs. ACWA (Paterson, NJ), 10/14/70, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  [Folder entitled 5(A-C)] #S-108 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Holiday Questionnaire, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Holiday Pay
- Manhattan Shirt Co. vs. ACWA(Charleston, SC), 5/29/70, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  #S-109 Decision Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Falsification, Work Stoppage
- Arrow Co., Div. of Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA, (Chester, NY) (Box 49, Folder 17)
  #S-110 Correspondence
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA 8/28/70, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  #S-111 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - #S-105 Layoff; #S-106 Rates of Pay; #S-111 Transfers (Demotion)
- Manhattan Shirt Co. vs. ACWA (Jessup, Ga.), 2/25/71, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  #S-129 (See 50-15, #S-130) - Falsification
- Manhattan Shirt Co. vs. ACWA (Jessup, Ga.) 2/25/71, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  #S-130 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - #S-129 Falsification; #S-130 Plant Rules
- Cluett, Peabody & Co., Inc.. vs. ACWA (Atlanta, Ga.) 5/15/71, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  #S-131 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Theft, Burden of Proof
- Manhattan Shirt Co. vs. ACWA (Americus, Ga.) (Box 50, Folder 17)
  #S-132 Correspondence
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA (Cedartown, Ga.) (Box 50, Folder 18)
  #S-133 Correspondence - Reporting Pay
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA (Chester, NY) (Box 50, Folder 19)
  #S-135 Correspondence - Bidding
- F. Jacobson, & Son vs. ACWA (Seymour, Indiana) 10/20/71, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  [Folder entitled 20(A-B)] #S-137 Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - Rates of Pay
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA (Leominster, Mass.), 1971 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  [Folder entitled 21(A-B)] #S-139 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Closing of Plant
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA (Atlanta, Ga.) 6/19/72 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  #S-141 Correspondence - Suspension
- Cluett, Peabody & Co. vs. ACWA (Atlanta, Ga.) 6/19/72 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  #S-152 Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Rates of Pay, Management Rights, Incentive System
- Brooklyn Union Gas Co. vs. Local 101 TWUA, 5/13/66, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  Compensation (Retirement Benefits)
- Brooklyn Union Gas Co. (BUGC) vs. Local 101, TWUA, 6/16/66, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  Decision - Compensation, Absences
- BUGC vs. Local 101, TWUA, 9/2/66, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  Decision - Arbitrability, Safely, Working Conditions, Assignment of Jobs, Management Right
- BUGC vs. Local 101, TWUA, 10/25/66, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  Decision - Assignment of Jobs, Evaluation of Job Factors
- BUGC vs. Local 101, TWUA, 3/27/79, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  Decision - Classification of Job, Assignment to Work Outside Classification, arbitrability
- BUGC vs. Local 101, TWUA, 4/13/67, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  Decision - Assignment to Work Outside Classification, Promotion
- BUGC vs. Local 101, TWUA, 5/4/67, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  Decision - Removal of Work from Bargaining Unit, Withdrawal of Existing Benefits, Past Practice
- BUGC vs. Local 101, TWUA, 5/5/67, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  Decision - Classification of Jobs, Past Practice
- BUGC vs. Local 101, TWUA, 6/12/67, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  Decision - Bargaining Unit
- BUGC vs. Local 101, TWUA, 6/21/68, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  Decision - Improper Personal Conduct, Fights & Altercation
- BUGC vs. Local 101, TWUA, 8/13/68, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  Decision - Overtime
- BUGC vs. Local 101, TWUA, 9/29/69, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  [Folder entitled 12(A-B)] Decision - Tardiness
- BUGC vs. Local 101, TWUA, Bills dated 10/28/65 - 1/29/69, 1965-1969 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- BUGC vs. Local 101, TWUA - General Correspondence, 4/12/65 - 6/30/71, 1965-1971 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  [Folder entitled 14(A-C)]
- BUGC vs. Local 101, TWUA, 3/23/70, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  Case #97 Hearing Transcript
- Text digitized from the collection. (Box 52)